The social climate that we're in right now with the trans community, especially my trans women of color.
I'm sorry, I don't have a problem with...
No, but it's like all lives matter and black lives matter.
It's like, yes, all trans lives matter.
We must acknowledge that black trans women are under attack exponentially in a greater way.
That's it!
You said it.
S***.
The social climate that we're in right now with the trans community, especially my trans women of color.
I'm sorry, I don't have a problem with...
No, but it's like all lives matter and black lives matter.
It's like, yes, all trans lives matter.
We must acknowledge that black trans women are under attack exponentially in a greater way.
That's it!
You said it.
S***.